<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Zuglo Tourist Guide</string>

    <!-- Sight texts -->
    <string name="heroes_square_title">Heroes\' Square</string>
    <string name="heroes_square_description">Heroes\' Square is one of the major squares
        in Budapest, Hungary, noted for its iconic statue complex featuring the Seven Chieftains
        of the Magyars and other important national leaders, as well as the Tomb
        of the Unknown Soldier.</string>

    <string name="vajdahunyad_castle_title">Vajdahunyad Castle</string>
    <string name="vajdahunyad_castle_description">Vajdahunyad Castle is a castle in the City Park
        of Budapest, Hungary. It was built in 1896 as part of the Millennial Exhibition which
        celebrated the 1,000 years of Hungary since the Hungarian Conquest of the Carpathian Basin
        in 895.</string>

    <string name="timewheel_title">Timewheel</string>
    <string name="timewheel_description">The Timewheel is one of the world\'s largest clepsammias,
        situated in Budapest next to City Park, right of Heroes\' Square and behind the Palace
        of Art (Műcsarnok), on the site of a former statue of Lenin that now stands in Memento Park.
        It is made of granite, steel, and glass, and weighs 60 tons.</string>

    <string name="anonymus_title">Anonymus Sculpture</string>
    <string name="anonymus_description">Anonymus Bele regis notarius ("Anonymous Notary
        of King Bela") or Master P. (fl. late 12th century – early 13th century) was the notary
        and chronicler of a Hungarian King, probably Béla III. Little is known about him, but
        his latinized name began with P, as he referred to himself as "P. dictus magister".</string>

    <string name="millenaris_velodrom_title">Millenáris Velodrom</string>
    <string name="millenaris_velodrom_description">Millenáris Sporttelep is a multi-use velodrome
        in Budapest, Hungary. It is currently used mostly for cycling events but has also been used
        for football matches. The venue has a capacity of 8,130 spectators and it opened in 1896.
        The track is 412 m (451 yd) and made of concrete.</string>

    <!-- Museum texts -->
    <string name="agricultural_museum_title">Hungarian Agricultural Museum</string>
    <string name="agricultural_museum_description">The biggest agricultural museum of Europe was
        founded in the Vajdahunyad Castle of the City Park, Budapest. The building itself is
        unique; too, for its architect Ignác Alpár merged various styles by using single parts
        of significant buildings found in Hungary at the time.</string>
    <string name="agricultural_museum_url">
        http://www.museum.hu/museum/57/Museum_and_Library_of_Hungarian_Agriculture</string>

    <string name="geological_institute_title">Geological Institute</string>
    <string name="geological_institute_description">The Geological Museum of Budapest is the main
        museum of geology in Hungary. It is located on the Stefánia út in the western part of Pest.</string>
    <string name="geological_institute_url">http://www.mfgi.hu/en</string>

    <string name="museum_of_fine_arts_title">Museum of Fine Arts</string>
    <string name="museum_of_fine_arts_description">The Museum of Fine Arts is a museum in Heroes\'
        Square, Budapest, Hungary, facing the Palace of Art. The museum\'s collection is made up
        of international art (other than Hungarian), including all periods of European art, and
        comprises more than 100,000 pieces.</string>
    <string name="museum_of_fine_arts_url">http://www.szepmuveszeti.hu/main</string>

    <string name="transportation_museum_title">Hungarian Technical and Transportation Museum</string>
    <string name="transportation_museum_description">Hungarian Technical and Transportation Museum
        is a museum in Budapest, Hungary. It is one of Europe’s oldest transportation collections.
        The museum has a unique collection of locomotives and railway cars on a 1:5 scale.</string>
    <string name="transportation_museum_url">http://www.mmkm.hu/index.php/en</string>

    <string name="hall_of_arts_title">Hall of Arts</string>
    <string name="hall_of_arts_description">The museum building is on Heroes\' Square, facing
        the Budapest Museum of Fine Arts. The art museum hosts temporary exhibits contemporary art.
        It operates on the program of German Kunsthalles, as an institution run by artists that
        does not maintain its own collection.</string>
    <string name="hall_of_arts_url">http://www.mucsarnok.hu/index1.php</string>

    <!-- Freetime activity texts -->
    <string name="ice_rink_title">Ice Rink in City Park</string>
    <string name="ice_rink_description">The City Park Ice Rink is a public ice rink located in
        the City Park of the Hungarian capital Budapest, between the Heroes\' Square and
        the Vajdahunyad Castle. Opened in 1870, it is the largest and one of the oldest ice rinks
        in Europe.</string>
    <string name="ice_rink_url">https://www.mujegpalya.hu/en</string>

    <string name="paskal_thermal_baths_title">Paskál Thermal Baths</string>
    <string name="paskal_thermal_baths_description">Paskál Thermal Baths located in the 14th
        district is the youngest baths in Budapest. The baths was expanded in 2016 with a covered
        wellness centre. Nowadays it offers 9 pools and various wellness services. The specialities
        of Paskál Thermal Baths are the outdoor aquabar and the unique geothermal sauna.</string>
    <string name="paskal_thermal_baths_url">http://en.paskalfurdo.hu/</string>

    <string name="circus_title">Capital Circus of Budapest</string>
    <string name="circus_description">The Capital Circus of Budapest is a circus building located
        in Budapest, Hungary. It originally opened in 1889, although it has changed locations
        since then. Its current building opened in 1971 and is the only stone circus
        in Central Europe.</string>
    <string name="circus_url">http://www.fnc.hu/</string>

    <string name="zoo_title">Budapest Zoo and Botanical Garden</string>
    <string name="zoo_description">Budapest Zoo &amp; Botanical Garden is the oldest zoo park
        in Hungary and one of the oldest in the world. It has 1,072 animal species and is located
        within Városliget Park, unusually for a zoo, it is in the centre of the city.</string>
    <string name="zoo_url">http://www.zoobudapest.com/en</string>

    <string name="szechenyi_thermal_baths_title">Széchenyi thermal bath</string>
    <string name="szechenyi_thermal_baths_description">The Széchenyi Medicinal Bath in Budapest is
        the largest medicinal bath in Europe. Its water is supplied by two thermal springs, their
        temperature is 74 °C (165 °F) and 77 °C (171 °F), respectively. Medical indications are
        on degenerative joint illnesses, chronic and sub-acute joint inflammations, as well
        as orthopaedic and traumatological post-treatments.</string>
    <string name="szechenyi_thermal_baths_url">Széchenyi thermal bath</string>

    <!-- Bar texts -->
    <string name="kertem_title">Kertem</string>
    <string name="kertem_description">The favorite spot of Balkan burger fanatics and local cyclists
        is situated far from the buzz of downtown, in Városliget. Due to Liget Project, aka.
        the renovation works at the City Park this locale now operates in the Olof Palme House and
        in its garden.</string>
    <string name="kertem_address">1146 Budapest, Olof Palme sétány 3</string>

    <string name="pantlika_title">Pántlika Bistro</string>
    <string name="pantlika_description">The run-down, deprived building was renovated insideout.
        Inside you find a retro bar which reflects the athmosphere of the ’60s and ’70s. All
        interior        objects and furniture aremaster pieces of the socialist industry.</string>
    <string name="pantlika_address">1146 Budapest, Hermina st 47</string>

    <string name="durer_kert_title">Dürer Kert</string>
    <string name="durer_kert_description">The building of Dürer Kert has started its long and
        curious transformation as a boarding school in the 19th century, ran by French nuns
        of Sacre Coeur. The complex had served as a Soviet college after WWII until 1989 when it was
        assigned to a prestigious Hungarian university</string>
    <string name="durer_kert_address">1146 Budapest, Ajtósi Dürer sor 19–21.</string>

    <string name="varosliget_cafe_title">Városliget Café &amp; Bar</string>
    <string name="varosliget_cafe_description">Városliget Café &amp; Bar is a restaurant and café
        in a historic building that was thoroughly renovated in 2013, surrounded by a fabulous
        environment in front of a beautiful lake. As its name indicates, it is in one of the most
        loveable parks of the city, Városliget (City Park), in an urban palace, giving the place
        both a nostalgic and a modern atmosphere.</string>
    <string name="varosliget_cafe_address">1146 Budapest, Olof Palme stny. 5</string>

    <string name="pedal_bar_title">Pedal Bar</string>
    <string name="pedal_bar_description">Pedal Bar is a unique way to drink fine beer while riding
        a special beer bike. Check out our Pedal Bar with your friends, drink draft beer and have
        fun when passing by the most famous sights of Budapest!</string>
    <string name="pedal_bar_address">Budapest, Heroes\' square</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
